draw three mutually tangent unit circles
like this these three circles enclose an
area as shown here can you determine the
area of the enclosed shape pause the
video and think about it before I show
you an answer one way to answer this
problem is to realize that the centers
of the three circles can be connected to
form an equilateral triangle with a side
length of two this has an area ofare <
TK of three but then this equilateral
triangle can be decomposed into these
three wedge shaped pieces in the area we
want each of the wed shaped pieces has
an area ofk 6 so the area we want is the
< TK 3 - 3 * > 6 which simplifies to the
< of 3 - pi/ 2 let me know in the
comments if you solved it a different
way